SEBASTIAN VAZQUEZ

PRODUCTION COORDINATOR

INTRODUCTION

26-years-old Production Coordinator with 3+ years of experience in 3D/2D animation studios and video game companies from Buenos Aires, Argentina. Graduated as Multimedia Designer from Universidad de Palermo Moved to Toronto in May 2018 with an open work permit and currently seeking for job opportunities.

CONTACT

1532 - 525 Adelaide St W, Toronto, Ontario, M5V 0N7

t: 437-353-8810 | e: vazq.seba@gmail.com w: sebastian-vazquez.com.ar in: linkedin.com/in/sebavazquez

EXPERIENCE

Lemonchili

February 2016 - April 2018

Production Coordinator / Manager

Worked as a link between the programming, art and game design departments, managing teams and ensuring quality standards and deadlines are met on each assignment, as well as leading the 3D department.

Worked closely with the marketing and social media departments to push advertising and brand campaigns.

Participated in projects such as Floyd's Sticker Jam (Google Indie Latam 3rd place winner), Tough Coded: Live, Tower Power (on closed beta) and Boop Kids (TBR).

Peppermelon

February 2015 - February 2016

Producer

Worked closely with clients such as DU Telecom, FOX, Ceska Sporitelna Bank, amongst others

Managed schedules, budgets and scripts as well as overseeing technically and artistically the outsourcing partners and in-house art direction team.

Freelance

March 2011 - November 2014

Desianer

Designed user interfaces for a variety of web projects and clients.

EDUCATION

Universidad de Palermo

March 2010 - December 2014

Diseño de Imagen y Sonido (Image and Sound Design)

Production / CG oriented. Won multiple awards for best of term projects.

Graduated with cum laude honors.

Image Campus

February 2013 - March 2014

Visual Effects and Compositing

One year course for visual effects compositing and CG. Worked with Maya and Nuke.

Image Campus

March 2012 - May 2012

Autodesk Maya Full

Two months in-depth Maya learning course.

SKILLS

Strong organizational skills Solid technical knowledge Innovative problem solver Strong management skills. Detail oriented

Able to adapt and work under pressure Team oriented

ACKNOWLEDGEMENTS

16 awards and acknowledgements received between 2010 and 2014, including publications, best of term projects and short films.

TOOLS

Maya - Arnold - Photoshop - After Effects - Shotgun - Zbrush Nuke - Unity - Office Package

LANGUAGES

Spanish Native speaker **English**Fluent in writing and

speaking.